volunteerhub.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Statement - VolunteerHub Protects Volunteer Organizations

CEI is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement applies to the data collected by CEI through the CEI VolunteerHub Web sites, CEI VolunteerHub services, and associated software (the “Services”). This privacy statement does not apply to data collected through other online or offline CEI sites, products or services.

**Collecting Your Business Information**

Information that is provided by organization administrators such as event information, attendee lists, or contact information, and any content uploaded to our servers by administrators (“Business Information”) are considered confidential to the subscribing organization. We will not view Business Information except as necessary to appropriately support the service. We will use Business Information for the purpose of service capacity planning; anticipating, diagnosing, supporting or resolving any problems that might limit or disrupt the Services; and improving the quality of the Services. Any Business Information collected during the meeting is also used to facilitate debugging during development, or to debug customer escalations that are being reproduced in real time.

**Collecting Your Personal Information**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you. The personal information we collect may include your name, postal address, email address, telephone number, facsimile number, company name, job title, and information about your company as well as information about the nature of your usage of our service, including the number of event registrants, duration and frequency of events, and total number of events.

We may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Web site; the pages that you access while at the Web site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the Services, analyze trends, and administer the Services.

**Use of Personal Information**

The personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized.

In support of these uses, CEI may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Site and any related CEI products or services, and to make the Site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Site to your particular preference or interests.

We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including critical updates and notifications. Additionally, with your permission, we may send you information about other CEI products and services, and/or share information with CEI partners so they may send you information about their products and services.

CEI occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as Web site hosting, packaging, mailing and delivering prizes, answering customer questions about products and services, and sending information about our products, special offers, and other new services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

CEI may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on CEI or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights of property of CEI and its family of Web sites, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of CEI employees, users of CEI products or services, or members of the public.

Please be aware that Carr Engineering Inc. may be required to disclose an individual’s personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. Carr Engineering Inc. may be liable for appropriate onward transfers of personal data to third parties.

Personal information collected by VolunteerHub may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which CEI or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer or information outside of your country.

**Control of Your Personal Information**

Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide related to the Services will not be shared outside of CEI and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission.

With regard to personal information that is collected at registration from our users (e.g. name, user ID, email address), we present the option not to receive communications regarding the Services. Customers who no longer wish to receive communications may opt-out or unsubscribe from receiving these communications. Each communication will have a way to unsubscribe from that list. If you encounter any difficulty, please email us at [support@volunteerhub.com](mailto:support@volunteerhub.com). Please be aware that this privacy statement and the choices you make related to the Services will not apply to personal information you may have provided to CEI in the context of other, separately operated, CEI products or services.

**Access to Personal Information**

CEI acknowledges an individual’s right of access to their personal information. If your personally identifiable information changes, we will provide a way to correct or update your personal data. Customers can log in and click on the Your Account link to modify personal information. VolunteerHub customers also may contact [support@volunteerhub.com](mailto:support@volunteerhub.com).

**Security of Your Personal Information**

CEI is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities.

We do not disclose your private, online communications. However, what you publish to your VolunteerHub service is available to those whom you authorize to see the information. In the event that you elect not to use any of the services security access controls, the content that you publish is available to those in the general public who are aware of the URL address for your event.

**Use of Cookies**

We use cookies on this site to ensure the integrity of the registration process and to personalize the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases site navigation, and so on. When you return to the web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the site’s features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to use interactive features of this or other web sites that depend on cookies.

**Enforcement of this Privacy Statement**

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should contact CEI by e-mail at [support@volunteerhub.com](mailto:support@volunteerhub.com).

**Changes to the Privacy Statement**

We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will revise the “last updated” date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our web site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the Services constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

**Contact Information**

CEI VolunteerHub welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you have questions about this statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us by e-mail or postal mail at the address provided below, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

VolunteerHub  
Carr Engineering Inc.  
5433 Haverhill Dr.  
Dublin, Ohio, 43017

To find other contact details for VolunteerHub, see [www.volunteerhub.com.](http://www.volunteerhub.com/)

**EU-US Privacy Shield Information**

CEI complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries.  CEI has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability.  If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has jurisdiction over CEI’s compliance with the Privacy Shield.

In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, CEI commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information.  European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact CEI at:

complaints@carr-engineering.com

CEI has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles BBB EU PRIVACY SHEILD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/](http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/) for more information and to file a complaint. Finally, as a last resort and in limited situations, EU individuals may seek redress from the Privacy Shield Panel, a binding arbitration mechanism.
